<archimate:DataObject
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Bundle"
    id="id-f29a06754d794efbad650964ae299ac1"
    documentation="One common operation performed with resources is to gather a collection of resources into a single instance with containing context. In FHIR this is referred to as &quot;bundling&quot; the resources together. These resource bundles are useful for a variety of different reasons, including:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;- Returning a set of resources that meet some criteria as part of a server operation (see RESTful Search)&#xD;&#xA;- Returning a set of versions of resources as part of the history operation on a server (see History)&#xD;&#xA;- Sending a set of resources as part of a message exchange (see Messaging)&#xD;&#xA;- Grouping a self-contained set of resources to act as an exchangeable and persistable collection with clinical integrity - e.g. a clinical document (see Documents)&#xD;&#xA;- Creating/updating/deleting a set of resources on a server as a single operation (including doing so as a single atomic transaction) (see Transactions)&#xD;&#xA;- Storing a collection of resources&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;http://hl7.org/fhir/R4/bundle.html&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Google translate  - Een veel voorkomende bewerking die met resources  wordt uitgevoerd, is het verzamelen van een verzameling resources in één exemplaar met daarin de context. In FHIR wordt dit het samenbundelen van de resources genoemd. Deze resourcebundels zijn om verschillende redenen nuttig, waaronder:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;- Het retourneren van een set resources die aan bepaalde criteria voldoen als onderdeel van een serverbewerking (zie RESTful Search)&#xD;&#xA;- Het retourneren van een reeks versies van resources als onderdeel van de geschiedenisbewerking op een server (zie Geschiedenis)&#xD;&#xA;- Een reeks resources verzenden als onderdeel van een berichtenuitwisseling (zie Berichten)&#xD;&#xA;- Het groeperen van een op zichzelf staande reeks resources om te fungeren als een uitwisselbare en persistente verzameling met klinische integriteit - b.v. een klinisch document (zie Documenten)&#xD;&#xA;- Het aanmaken/bijwerken/verwijderen van een set resources op een server als een enkele handeling (inclusief dit als een enkele atomaire transactie) (zie Transacties)&#xD;&#xA;- Het opslaan van een verzameling resources"/>
