<archimate:DataObject
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="MedicationStatement"
    id="id-0bc936d35ee04d20af2320095923b9a4"
    documentation="A record of a medication that is being consumed by a patient. A MedicationStatement may indicate that the patient may be taking the medication now or has taken the medication in the past or will be taking the medication in the future. The source of this information can be the patient, significant other (such as a family member or spouse), or a clinician. A common scenario where this information is captured is during the history taking process during a patient visit or stay. The medication information may come from sources such as the patient's memory, from a prescription bottle, or from a list of medications the patient, clinician or other party maintains.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The primary difference between a medication statement and a medication administration is that the medication administration has complete administration information and is based on actual administration information from the person who administered the medication. A medication statement is often, if not always, less specific. There is no required date/time when the medication was administered, in fact we only know that a source has reported the patient is taking this medication, where details such as time, quantity, or rate or even medication product may be incomplete or missing or less precise. As stated earlier, the medication statement information may come from the patient's memory, from a prescription bottle or from a list of medications the patient, clinician or other party maintains. Medication administration is more formal and is not missing detailed information.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;https://hl7.org/fhir/R4/medicationstatement.html&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Google translate  - Een registratie van een medicijn dat door een patiënt wordt gebruikt. Uit een MedicationStatement kan blijken dat de patiënt de medicijnen nu gebruikt, in het verleden heeft gebruikt of in de toekomst gaat gebruiken. De bron van deze informatie kan de patiënt, een partner (zoals een familielid of echtgenoot) of een arts zijn. Een veel voorkomend scenario waarin deze informatie wordt vastgelegd, is tijdens het anamneseproces tijdens een bezoek of verblijf van een patiënt. De medicatie-informatie kan afkomstig zijn uit bronnen zoals het geheugen van de patiënt, uit een receptflesje of uit een lijst met medicijnen die de patiënt, arts of andere partij bijhoudt.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Het voornaamste verschil tussen een MedicationStatement en een MedicationAdministration is dat de medicatieadministratie volledige toedieningsinformatie bevat en gebaseerd is op daadwerkelijke toedieningsinformatie van degene die de medicatie heeft toegediend. Een medicatieverklaring is vaak, zo niet altijd, minder specifiek. Er is geen vereiste datum/tijd waarop het medicijn werd toegediend. In feite weten we alleen dat een bron heeft gemeld dat de patiënt dit medicijn gebruikt, waarbij details zoals tijd, hoeveelheid of snelheid of zelfs het medicijnproduct onvolledig kunnen zijn of ontbreken of minder nauwkeurig. Zoals eerder vermeld, kan de medicatieverklaringinformatie afkomstig zijn uit het geheugen van de patiënt, uit een receptflesje of uit een lijst met medicijnen die de patiënt, arts of andere partij bijhoudt. Medicatieadministratie is formeler en er ontbreekt geen gedetailleerde informatie."/>
