<archimate:DataObject
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Binary"
    id="id-3c33b5dd21bb44eea6253f4d81f7305c"
    documentation="There are situations where it is useful or required to handle pure binary content using the same framework as other resources. Typically, this is when the binary content is referred to from other FHIR Resources. Using the same framework means that the existing servers, security arrangements, code libraries, etc. can handle additional related content. Typically, Binary resources are used for handling content such as:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;- CDA Documents (i.e. with XDS)&#xD;&#xA;- PDF Documents&#xD;&#xA;- Images&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A binary resource can contain any content, whether text, image, pdf, zip archive, etc. These resources are served in their native form on the rest interface, but can also be represented in XML, JSON, or other formats, such as when including these resources in a Bundle (used when it is convenient to include these in the response directly rather than leaving them by reference).&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;http://hl7.org/fhir/R4/binary.html&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Google translate  - Er zijn situaties waarin het nuttig of vereist is om pure binaire inhoud te verwerken met hetzelfde raamwerk als andere resources. Meestal is dit het geval wanneer naar de binaire inhoud wordt verwezen vanuit andere FHIR-resources. Het gebruik van hetzelfde raamwerk betekent dat de bestaande servers, beveiligingsregelingen, codebibliotheken, enz. aanvullende gerelateerde inhoud kunnen verwerken. Normaal gesproken worden binaire resources gebruikt voor het verwerken van inhoud zoals:&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;- CDA-documenten (d.w.z. met XDS)&#xD;&#xA;- PDF-documenten&#xD;&#xA;- Afbeeldingen&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Een binaire resource kan elke inhoud bevatten, of het nu gaat om tekst, afbeeldingen, pdf, zip-archief, enz. Deze bronnen worden in hun oorspronkelijke vorm aangeboden op de restinterface, maar kunnen ook worden weergegeven in XML, JSON of andere formaten, zoals wanneer het opnemen van deze resources in een bundel (gebruikt wanneer het handig is om deze direct in het antwoord op te nemen in plaats van ze als referentie te laten staan)."/>
